Guide to the Public Art Fund Archive 1966-2009 MSS.270
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series X: Video, 179240
  - Subseries X.B: Originals, 197027
    - "Spider Exhibit/Rockefeller Plaza", 2001; 197792 (Box 99, Media ID: 270.0187)
    - Jenny Holzer-Xenon Projections, Monterrey Mexico (tape 1 of 4), 2001; 197798 (Box 99, Media ID: 270.0188)
    - Jenny Holzer-Xenon Projections, Monterrey Mexico - (Tape 3 of 4), 2001; 197799 (Box 99, Media ID: 270.0189)
    - Target Art in the Park on "Good Day New York", 2001; 197800 (Box 99, Media ID: 270.0190)
    - "Firemen's Memorial", ABC, Ivan + Elliot Schwartz, 2001; 197801 (Box 99, Media ID: 270.0191)
    - "Tom Eccles-Public Art Fund" - Eyewitness News, 2001; 197802 (Box 99, Media ID: 270.0192)
    - WTC Public Art, 2001; 197803 (Box 99, Media ID: 270.0193)
    - "There Are Things that Move Outside of Motion" - Lawrence Weiner, 2001; 197806 (Box 99, Media ID: 270.0194)
    - Louise Bourgeois: "Spiders", 2001; 197807 (Box 99, Media ID: 270.0195)
    - Louise Bourgeois: "Spiders" - Coverage, 2001; 197808 (Box 99, Media ID: 270.0196)
    - Gustavo Artigas - "The Rules of the Game", 2001; 197809 (Box 99, Media ID: 270.0197)
      TRT: 00:12:00
    - Martin Creed - "Illuminations", 2001; 197810 (Box 99, Media ID: 270.0198)
    - "Tom Eccles & Susan Freedman", 2002; 197811 (Box 99, Media ID: 270.0199)
      TRT: 00:02:24
    - "I Love Taxi" - Tent Installation, Test in Studio, by Chiang Mai - Navin Rawanchaikul, 2001; 197812 (Box 99, Media ID: 270.0200)
    - "Stainless Steel Tree", 2002; 197813 (Box 99, Media ID: 270.0201)
    - "Art in Central Park", 2002; 197814 (Box 99, Media ID: 270.0202)
    - Fischer Spooner EPK/Optic Nerve, 2002; 197815 (Box 99, Media ID: 270.0203)
    - "Public Art Fund--Pies", 2002; 197816 (Box 99, Media ID: 270.0204)
      TRT: 00:02:45
    - "Multiple Segments", 2002; 197817 (Box 99, Media ID: 270.0205)
    - Pies Pkg. - FOX - Anissa Mack, 2002; 197818 (Box 99, Media ID: 270.0206)
      TRT: 00:04:40
    - Nam June Paik - Rehearsal, 2002; 197819 (Box 100, Media ID: 270.0207)
      TRT: 01:02:40
    - "Nam June Paik" - Today in New York, 2002; 197820 (Box 100, Media ID: 270.0208)
      TRT: 00:03:34
    - "MOMA Moving", 2002; 197821 (Box 100, Media ID: 270.0209)
    - "Tom Eccles" - Sunday Today in New York - WNBC-TV (NBC), 2002; 197822 (Box 100, Media ID: 270.0210)
      TRT: 00:01:31
    - "Tom Eccles" - News All Day, 2002; 197823 (Box 100, Media ID: 270.0211)
      TRT: 00:03:22
    - New Yorkers - Art Special, 2002; 197824 (Box 100, Media ID: 270.0212)
    - Street Procession Film by Francis Alÿs + Rafael Ortega, 2002; 197825 (Box 100, Media ID: 270.0213)
    - "Target Art in the Park" on "Weekend Today in New York", 2002; 197826 (Box 100, Media ID: 270.0214)
    - "Target Art in the Park" - New York 1 News, 2002; 197827 (Box 100, Media ID: 270.0215)
    - "The Modern Procession" - Long Play (Audio still in Process) - Not for Public Use, 2002; 197869 (Box 100, Media ID: 270.0216)
    - American's for the Arts, 2003; 197870 (Box 100, Media ID: 270.0217)
    - "Metrospective", 2003; 197871 (Box 100, Media ID: 270.0218)
    - "City Hall Park", 2003; 197872 (Box 100, Media ID: 270.0219)
      TRT: 00:02:23
    - "Public Art Fund" - News All Day, 2003; 197873 (Box 100, Media ID: 270.0220)
      TRT: 00:02:56
    - "Picnic Tables", 2003; 197877 (Box 100, Media ID: 270.0221)
      TRT: 00:02:41
    - "Japanese Artist/Takashi Murakami", 2003; 197878 (Box 100, Media ID: 270.0222)
      TRT: 00:02:31
    - "Tom Eccles/Public Art Fund", 2003; 197879 (Box 100, Media ID: 270.0223)
      TRT: 00:02:37
    - "Museum of Jewish Heritage", 2003; 197880 (Box 100, Media ID: 270.0224)
      TRT: 00:02:53
    - "Museum of Jewish Heritage/Public Art Fund", 2003; 197881 (Box 100, Media ID: 270.0225)
      TRT: 00:09:25
    - "Sunday Morning" - Andy Goldsworthy, 2003; 197883 (Box 100, Media ID: 270.0226)
    - "Roy Lichtenstein Artwork/City Hall", 2003; 197884 (Box 100, Media ID: 270.0228)
    - "Amei Wallach/Public Art Fund", 2003; 197885 (Box 100, Media ID: 270.0229)
      TRT: 00:10:34
    - Jewish Museum - Andy Goldsworthy's Video Footage of Process, 2003; 197886 (Box 100, Media ID: 270.0230)
    - The Charlie Rose Show US/Japanese Relations Special - Takashi Murakami mentioned, 2003; 197887 (Box 100, Media ID: 270.0231)
    - NY1 WTC roundtable, 2003; 197888 (Box 100, Media ID: 270.0232)
    - "Dream Temple" - Documentation at Malmo - Mariko Mori, 2003; 197889 (Box 100, Media ID: 270.0233)
    - [2003], 197890 (Box 100, Media ID: 270.0234)
    - "Public Art Fund/Andy Rooney/Modern Art", 2004; 197891 (Box 100, Media ID: 270.0235)
    - "Daddy's Big Head/Central Park/Paul McCartney", 2004; 197892 (Box 100, Media ID: 270.0236)
    - "Whitney Museum/Public Art Fund", 2004; 197893 (Box 100, Media ID: 270.0237)
      TRT: 00:02:47
    - "Public Art Fund/Tom Eccles/WTC Memorial Center", 2004; 197894 (Box 100, Media ID: 270.0238)
      TRT: 00:02:10
    - Public Art Fund - Projects in Central Park - April 17th, 2004 - Edited Version, 197897 (Box 100, Media ID: 270.0239)
    - Assume Vivid Astro Focus, 2004; 197898 (Box 101, Media ID: 270.0240)
    - Central Park - Assume vivid [astro focus], 2004; 197899 (Box 101, Media ID: 270.0241)
    - "Public Art Fund/Central Park/Audio/Exhibit", 2004; 197900 (Box 101, Media ID: 270.0242)
      TRT: 00:02:38
    - "Public Art Fund/Tom Eccles/Lincoln Center", 2004; 197901 (Box 101, Media ID: 270.0243)
    - "Public Art Fund/Tom Eccles/Walking to the Sky", 2004; 197902 (Box 101, Media ID: 270.0244)
      TRT: 00:02:17
    - "Public Art Fund/Tom Eccles/Sculpture, 2004; 197904 (Box 101, Media ID: 270.0245)
    - "Artist Julian Opie", 2004; 197905 (Box 101, Media ID: 270.0246)
      TRT: 00:01:00
    - A Needle Woman - Kim Sooja, 2004; 197906 (Box 101, Media ID: 270.0247)
    - Short Version - "Waylay" - Brian Tolle / Video by Brian Dentz, 2004; 197907 (Box 101, Media ID: 270.0248)
    - "Tom Eccles/Public Art Fund", 2004; 197909 (Box 101, Media ID: 270.0249)
      TRT: 00:03:07
    - "Little Boy/Tom Eccles/Public Art Fund", 2005; 197911 (Box 101, Media ID: 270.0250)
    - "Alejandro Diaz/Public Art Fund", 2005; 197912 (Box 101, Media ID: 270.0251)
    - Public Art Fund-Japanese Pop Art Show, 2005; 197914 (Box 101, Media ID: 270.0252)
    - Doris Freedman Award, 2005; 197915 (Box 101, Media ID: 270.0253)
    - Public Art Fund/New York Market/Cable Market, 2005; 197916 (Box 101, Media ID: 270.0255)
    - Rockefeller Structure Segment, 2006; 197917 (Box 101, Media ID: 270.0256)
      TRT: 00:03:11
    - Rockefeller Center Structure - Cable Market, 2006; 197918 (Box 101, Media ID: 270.0257)
      TRT: 00:00:22
    - Rockefeller Structure Segment - New York Market, 2006; 197919 (Box 101, Media ID: 270.0258)
      TRT: 00:03:01
    - "Sky Mirror - Tumi", 2006; 197920 (Box 101, Media ID: 270.0259)
    - Chelsea Studios - The Public Art Fund, 2006; 197923 (Box 101, Media ID: 270.0260)
      Format: DVCPro
      TRT: 00:07:52
    - "Towards a Livable City", 2006; 197924 (Box 101, Media ID: 270.0261)
    - PAF 30th Anniversary Video, 2006; 197925 (Box 101, Media ID: 270.0262)
      TRT: 00:14:48
    - Anish Kapoor, London 2007, 197942 (Box 101, Media ID: 270.0263)
      Format: DVCam
    - Rachel Whiteread - April 18th, 2007, 197943 (Box 101, Media ID: 270.0264)
    - Bloomberg Television - Waterfalls Footage - Air, Sea, Land - Part One, 2008; 197937 (Box 101, Media ID: 270.0265)
      Format: HDCam
    - Bloomberg Television - Waterfalls Footage - Air, Sea, Land - Part Two, 2008; 197938 (Box 101, Media ID: 270.0266)
    - AIDS Concert Demo Reel, undated; 197958 (Box 101, Media ID: 270.0267)
    - APEC Cai Gao-Quiang, undated; 198012 (Box 101, Media ID: 270.0268)
    - Art at Hilton Time Square, undated; 198015 (Box 101, Media ID: 270.0269)
    - City Arts Show 206 - La Dolce Vito, undated; 197955 (Box 101, Media ID: 270.0271)
    - Evil Clowns. They steal presents and kill other innocent, well-meaning clowns., undated; 197960 (Box 101, Media ID: 270.0272)
      TRT: 00:04:37
    - Ilya Kabakov - Fox5, undated; 197952 (Box 101, Media ID: 270.0533)
    - "In the Public Realm" News Coverage, undated; 197954 (Box 101, Media ID: 270.0534)
    - Jewish Museum: Andy Goldsworthy, undated; 198024 (Box 102, Media ID: 270.0535)
    - Keith Haring on Park - Bloomberg TV, undated; 198025 (Box 102, Media ID: 270.0536)
    - La Dolce Vito #206, undated; 197951 (Box 102, Media ID: 270.0537)
    - "Landscape Soundings" by Bill Fontana, undated; 198026 (Box 102, Media ID: 270.0538)
    - Main II - Unknown [Metal Sculpture by Watt], undated; 197956 (Box 102, Media ID: 270.0539)
    - [Nonsolomoda Servizio: "New York DIA Beacon"], undated; 197957 (Box 102, Media ID: 270.0540)
    - Pipilotti Rist - Opening Event, undated; 198035 (Box 102, Media ID: 270.0541)
    - Small News & Big News #6 - NY Unique Art News, undated; 197953 (Box 102, Media ID: 270.0542)
    - Tom Otterness - "New York Views" Ch7, undated; 198036 (Box 102, Media ID: 270.0543)
    - Tom Otterness - Public Art Fund, undated; 198037 (Box 102, Media ID: 270.0544)
    - "Trans-Voices", undated; 197946 (Box 102, Media ID: 270.0545)
    - Trans-Voices: Questions for a New Order, undated; 197947 (Box 102, Media ID: 270.0546)
      TRT: 00:08:54
    - Urban Paradise/Justen Ladda/Susan Freedman/Tom Eccles, undated; 198038 (Box 102, Media ID: 270.0547)
    - Video Drive-in Project, undated; 198039 (Box 102, Media ID: 270.0548)
    - [Duett Maneta NY-NTSC], undated; 197959 (Box 102, Media ID: 270.0549)
    - Dixon, undated; 198043 (Box 102, Media ID: 270.0550)
    - Trans-Voices: Questions for a New Order, undated; 198044 (Box 102, Media ID: 270.0551)
      TRT: 00:08:45
    - [Public Art Fund Examples], undated; 198050 (Box 102, Media ID: 270.0552)
    - Art Fund Copy, undated; 198051 (Box 102, Media ID: 270.0553)
    - Public Art Fund Tape for the FF., undated; 198056 (Box 102, Media ID: 270.0554)
    - Pipilotti Rist Opening Reception, undated; 198057 (Box 102, Media ID: 270.0555)
    - The Public Art Fund, undated; 198046 (Box 102, Media ID: 270.0556)
    - 30-Second PSA on AIDS By Bing Lee and Garson Yu / Cantonese, 1992; 198258 (Box 103, Media ID: 270.0557)
      Format: 1" open reel
    - 30-Second PSA on AIDS By Bing Lee and Garson Yu / English, 1992; 201154 (Box 103, Media ID: 270.0558)
    - 30-Second PSA on AIDS By Bing Lee and Garson Yu / English, 1992; 198259 (Box 103, Media ID: 270.0559)
    - 30-Second PSA on AIDS By Bing Lee and Garson Yu / Japanese, 1992; 198260 (Box 103, Media ID: 270.0560)
    - 30-Second PSA on AIDS By Bing Lee and Garson Yu / Korean, 1992; 198261 (Box 103, Media ID: 270.0561)
    - 30-Second PSA on AIDS By Bing Lee and Garson Yu / Mandarin, 1992; 198262 (Box 103, Media ID: 270.0562)
    - 30-Second PSA on AIDS By Bing Lee and Garson Yu / Cantonese (Master), 1992; 198263 (Box 103, Media ID: 270.0563)
    - 30-Second PSA on AIDS By Bing Lee and Garson Yu / English (Master), 1992; 198264 (Box 103, Media ID: 270.0564)
    - 30-Second PSA on AIDS By Bing Lee and Garson Yu / Korean (Master), 1992; 198265 (Box 103, Media ID: 270.0565)
    - 30-Second PSA on AIDS By Bing Lee and Garson Yu / Japanese (Master), 1992; 198266 (Box 103, Media ID: 270.0566)
    - 30-Second PSA on AIDS By Bing Lee and Garson Yu / Mandarin (Master), 1992; 198267 (Box 103, Media ID: 270.0567)
    - 30-Second PSA on AIDS By Bing Lee and Garson Yu / Multi-Reel (Master), 1992; 198268 (Box 103, Media ID: 270.0568)
- Series XI: Film, 197079
  This series contains film footage from the Public Art Fund Archive. Descriptions are derived from the original container annotations and include title, date, format, and the total running time (TRT).
  - "DFF" - Reel 1 - Pix, undated; 198252 (Reel 270.0273)
    Gauge: 16mm
  - "DFF" - Reel 1 - Mag Track, undated; 198279 (Reel 270.0274)
  - "DFF" - Reel 2 - Pix, undated; 198253 (Reel 270.0275)
  - "DFF" - Reel 2 - Mag Track, undated; 198280 (Reel 270.0276)
  - "DFF" - Reel 3 - Pix, undated; 198254 (Reel 270.0277)
  - "DFF" - Reel 3 - Mag Track, undated; 198255 (Reel 270.0278)
  - "DFF" - Reel 4 - Pix, undated; 198269 (Reel 270.0279)
  - "DFF" - Reel 4 - Mag Track, undated; 198270 (Reel 270.0280)
  - "DFF" - Reel 5 - Pix, undated; 198271 (Reel 270.0281)
  - "DFF" - Reel 5 - Mag Track, undated; 198272 (Reel 270.0282)
  - "DFF" - Reel 6 - Pix, undated; 198273 (Reel 270.0283)
  - "DFF" - Reel 6 - Mag Track, undated; 198274 (Reel 270.0284)
  - PAF Portraits - 30th Anniv Video - F1, undated; 198276 (Reel 270.0285)
  - PAF Portraits - 30th Anniv Video - F1, undated; 198275 (Reel 270.0286)
  - "DFF" - DIAL A, undated; 198277 (Reel 270.0287)
  - "DFF" - DIAL B, undated; 198278 (Reel 270.0288)
  - "DFF" - Slop Print (B&W Print) - Pix, undated; 198281 (Reel 270.0289)
  - "DFF" - Music A, undated; 198282 (Reel 270.0290)
  - "DFF" - Fx A, undated; 198283 (Reel 270.0291)
  - "DFF" - Fx B, undated; 198284 (Reel 270.0292)
  - "DFF" - Work Pix, undated; 198285 (Reel 270.0293 - 270.0294, Media ID: 270.0293)
  - "DFF" - Unidentified Element, undated; 198286 (Reel 270.0293 - 270.0294, Media ID: 270.0294)
  - "DFF" - Nevelson" MOS, undated; 201259 (Reel 270.0295 - 270.0297, Media ID: 270.0295)
  - "DFF" - "Rosenthal" MOS, undated; 201260 (Reel 270.0295 - 270.0297, Media ID: 270.0296)
  - "DFF" - "Murals/Sculpture/Peo" MOS, undated; 201261 (Reel 270.0295 - 270.0297, Media ID: 270.0297)
  - "DFF" - Misc. Buildings/Peo" MOS, undated; 201262 (Reel 270.0298 - 270.0301, Media ID: 270.0298)
  - "DFF" - "G.A. Plaza" MOS, undated; 201263 (Reel 270.0298 - 270.0301, Media ID: 270.0299)
  - "DFF" - "Select City" MOS, undated; 201264 (Reel 270.0298 - 270.0301, Media ID: 270.0300)
  - "DFF" - "City Select" MOS, undated; 201265 (Reel 270.0298 - 270.0301, Media ID: 270.0301)
  - "DFF" - "City From Rooftop" MOS, undated; 201266 (Reel 270.0302 - 270.0304, Media ID: 270.0302)
  - "DFF" - "Haas" MOS, undated; 201267 (Reel 270.0302 - 270.0304, Media ID: 270.0303)
  - "DFF" - "Cube/Nevelson Plaza" MOS, undated; 201268 (Reel 270.0302 - 270.0304, Media ID: 270.0304)
  - "DFF" - "Intv. Select #1", undated (Reel 270.0305)
  - "DFF" - "Intv. Select #2", undated (Reel 270.0306)
  - "DFF" - "Intv. Select #3", undated (Reel 270.0307)
  - "DFF" - "Intv. Select #4", undated (Reel 270.0308)
  - "DFF" - "Music" - "Outs", undated (Reel 270.0309)
  - "DFF" - "new Deal Films/EFX", undated (Reel 270.0310)
  - "DFF" - "Slides", undated (Reel 270.0311)
  - "DFF" - "Trims and Outs", undated (Reel 270.0312)
- Series XII: Audio, 179666
  This series contains audio recordings from the Public Art Fund Archive. The audio consists of recordings of lectures, panel discussions, interviews, news broadcasts, community hearings, and audio used as source material. The Audio reels titled "New Deal Films" correspond to a 16mm film, titled "Towards a Livable City" (Media ID 270.032 - Media ID: 270.0335) Descriptions are derived from the original cassette or container annotations and include title, date, the original format of audio, and the total running time (TRT).
  - Steve Carter Sept 18, 1970 / Mon Levinson Nov. 27 1970, 199465 (Box 104, Media ID: 270.0314)
    Format: 1/4" audiocassette
  - Lehman Collage - Public Art symposium - Dec 14 1971, 199466 (Box 104, Media ID: 270.0315)
  - Artist Community Meeting - Jan 11, 1972 - Planning Sculpture Neighborhood Exhibition, 199467 (Box 104, Media ID: 270.0316)
  - City Walls 3/24/73, 1973; 199468 (Box 104, Media ID: 270.0317)
  - Nina Grad '73, 1973; 199469 (Box 104, Media ID: 270.0318)
  - Smithtown - Community Presentation, 1976; 199470 (Box 104, Media ID: 270.0319)
  - Freedman Dedication Gallery, 1976; 199471 (Box 104, Media ID: 270.0320)
  - Art Commission Meeting '78, 1978; 199472 (Box 104, Media ID: 270.0321)
  - Sale Message, [1978]; 199473 (Box 104, Media ID: 270.0322)
  - D.C.F - Philadelphia Museum/Public Art-City Walls - 4/27/79, 1979; 199474 (Box 104, Media ID: 270.0323)
  - New Deal - 191426 / New Deal Films: "DFF" 2/82 - SR 6 Richard Haas in studio/ Tony Rosenthal in Astor Place, 1982; 199475 (Box 104, Media ID: 270.0324)
  - New Deal Films: "DFF" 3/82 - SR 9 Kenneth Snelson in studio/ T. Rosenthal; Kent Barwick Central Park, 1982; 199476 (Box 104, Media ID: 270.0325)
  - New Deal Films Inc. / Camera 1+2+3 Susan Randolph/Brendan Gill, 1982; 199477 (Box 104, Media ID: 270.0326)
  - New Deal Films Inc. / March 9, 1982 / Louise Nevelson Interview/ Sound Roll 4 Camera Roll 6, 199478 (Box 104, Media ID: 270.0327)
  - New Deal Films Inc. / Camera Roll 8+9/Sound Roll 5/ August Heckscher / John Lindsey/ March 9, 1982, 199479 (Box 104, Media ID: 270.0328)
  - New Deal Films Inc. / Paul Goldberger / Sound Roll [1 2 1]/ Camera Roll [3+4+1], 1982; 199480 (Box 104, Media ID: 270.0329)
  - New Deal Films Inc. / March 8, 1982 / Sound Roll 3 / Camera Roll 5 / Paul Goldberger / Mayor Koch, 199481 (Box 104, Media ID: 270.0330)
  - New Deal Films Inc. / Sound Roll 6 - 3/11/82 - D.F.F. / 71/2ips 60 HZ / 24 FPS 16mm stock sound #24-, 1982; 199482 (Box 104, Media ID: 270.0331)
  - New Deal Films Inc. / Roll 7 / Richard Haas ext- / Tony Rosenthal ", 1982; 199483 (Box 104, Media ID: 270.0332)
  - New Deal Films Inc. / Roll 8, 1982; 199484 (Box 104, Media ID: 270.0333)
  - New Deal Films Inc. / Roll 9, 1982; 199485 (Box 104, Media ID: 270.0334)
  - New Deal Films Inc. / 4/5/82 - Mark di Suvero - (Doris Freedman) [Long Island City], 1982; 199486 (Box 104, Media ID: 270.0335)
  - Hearing on relocation of Richard Serra Sculpture at 26 Federal Plaza, 1984; 199487 (Box 104, Media ID: 270.0336)
  - Community hearing re: Richard Serra sculpture at 26 federal Plaza/Foley square, 1984; 199510 (Box 105, Media ID: 270.0337)
  - Art in NYC ME 871127, 1987; 199511 (Box 105, Media ID: 270.0338)
  - Cologne/San Francisco Soundbridge / Sound sculptures by Bill Fontana / May 31, 1987, 199512 (Box 105, Media ID: 270.0339)
  - N.P.R. Weekend Edition #870426 6 mins. "Messages to the Public Alfredo Jaar / Public Art Fund / 4.26.87, 1987; 199513 (Box 105, Media ID: 270.0340)
  - Public Art Fund - Spectacolor billboard 1989 November / 800 Buy with Art, 199514 (Box 105, Media ID: 270.0341)
  - the MAS Fellows / Art in Public Spaces: Its Use + Abuse, 1990; 199515 (Box 105, Media ID: 270.0342)
  - WE 870426 / Art in Times Square, 1990; 199516 (Box 105, Media ID: 270.0343)
  - The new old west / ATC 900723, 1990; 199517 (Box 105, Media ID: 270.0344)
  - Fontana: NY Harbor (NY harbor, SF soundbridge), 1991; 199518 (Box 105, Media ID: 270.0345)
  - Bill Fontana - NY Harbor Gong Buoy, 1991; 199519 (Box 105, Media ID: 270.0346)
  - Benefit Speeches 6/6/91 (microcassette), 1991; 199520 (Box 105, Media ID: 270.0347)
  - Fontana: NY Harbor Bell Buoy, 1991; 199521 (Box 105, Media ID: 270.0348)
  - Public Art Fund [WQCD] - Nancy Newhouse - 6/16/91 / Susan Freedman/ Robert Ressler, 1991; 199522 (Box 105, Media ID: 270.0349)
  - Charted Collected and Carefully counted / Interview: Nicole R. [Akiesa Griffith], 1992; 199523 (Box 105, Media ID: 270.0350)
  - A Day Without Art / News Report aired on WBAI FM / December 1, 1992 / Produced by David Sears, 270.0351; 199524 (Box 105, Media ID: 270.0351, E-records fales_mss270, E-records 270.0351)
    Format: 1/4" audiocassette, Duration: 12 min. Side two is blank.
  - Trans- Voices sample tape - not for broadcast, 1992; 199525 (Box 105, Media ID: 270.0352)
    TRT: 00:25:00
  - Missing in Action / Public Art 3/23/93 #1, 1993; 199526 (Box 105, Media ID: 270.0353)
  - Missing in Action Public Art 3/23/93 #2, 1993; 199527 (Box 105, Media ID: 270.0354)
  - WNYC - July 22, 1993 / James Clark, Harriet [Seuie], Melinda Hunt, 199528 (Box 105, Media ID: 270.0355)
  - Botero in New York / WNCN - FN, 9/25/93 10:55 AM // Side B: Judith Shea Interview WNCN '93, 1993; 199529 (Box 105, Media ID: 270.0356)
  - 11/7/95 Tom Finkelpearl - Tuesday Night Talks, 1995; 199530 (Box 105, Media ID: 270.0357)
  - Tuesday Night Talks - Tom Finkelpearl 11/7/95, 1995; 199531 (Box 105, Media ID: 270.0358)
  - 11/14/95 Vito Acconci - Tuesday Night Talks, 1995; 199532 (Box 105, Media ID: 270.0359)
  - Tuesday Night Talks / Vito Acconci - 11/14/95 - Tape 1, 1995; 199533 (Box 105, Media ID: 270.0360)
  - Tuesday Night Talks / Vito Acconci - 11/14/95 - Tape 2, 1995; 199534 (Box 105, Media ID: 270.0361)
  - 11/21/95 Kristin Jones / Andrew Ginzel / Tuesday Night Talks, 1995; 199535 (Box 105, Media ID: 270.0362)
  - Tuesday Night Talks / Kristin Jones / Andrew Ginzel / 11/21/95 - 9327-4, 1995; 199536 (Box 105, Media ID: 270.0363)
  - 11/28/95 - Tom Otterness - Tuesday Night Talks, 1995; 199537 (Box 105, Media ID: 270.0364)
  - Tuesday night talks / Tom Otterness - 11/25/95, 1995; 199538 (Box 105, Media ID: 270.0365)
  - "What They Remember" - Composite (7:16) Public Art Fund inc. 05/05/95, 1995; 199539 (Box 105, Media ID: 270.0366)
    TRT: 00:07:16
  - "What They Remember" - Continuous 1kHz test tone. Pubic Art Fund inc. 05/05/95, 1995; 199540 (Box 105, Media ID: 270.0367)
  - "What They Remember" - Continuous 1kHz test tone. Pubic Art Fund inc. 05/05/95, 1995; 199541 (Box 105, Media ID: 270.0368)
  - "What They Remember" - Composite (7:16) Public Art Fund inc. 05/05/95, 1995; 199542 (Box 105, Media ID: 270.0369)
  - "What They Remember" - Dara Kenigsberg (2:17) Public Art Fund Inc. 05/05/95, 1995; 199543 (Box 105, Media ID: 270.0370)
  - "What They Remember" - Dara Kenigsberg (2:17) Public Art Fund Inc. 05/05/95, 1995; 199545 (Box 105, Media ID: 270.0371)
  - "What They Remember" - Ruthie Mirsky (7:53) Public Art Fund Inc. 05/05/95, 1995; 199544 (Box 105, Media ID: 270.0372)
    TRT: 00:07:53
  - "What They Remember" - Ruthie Mirsky (7:53) Public Art Fund Inc. 05/05/95, 1995; 199546 (Box 105, Media ID: 270.0373)
  - "What They Remember" - Sam Chen (3:35) Public Art Fund Inc. 05/05/95, 1995; 199547 (Box 105, Media ID: 270.0374)
    TRT: 00:03:35
  - "What They Remember" - Sarah Finkelstein (8:00) Public Art Fund Inc. 05/05/95, 1995; 199548 (Box 105, Media ID: 270.0375)
    TRT: 00:08:00
  - "What They Remember" - Yuri & Yana Abayev (5:04) Public Art Fund Inc. 05/05/95, 1995; 199549 (Box 105, Media ID: 270.0376)
    TRT: 00:05:04
  - "What They Remember" - Yuri & Yana Abayev (5:04) Public Art Fund Inc. 05/05/95, 1995; 199550 (Box 105, Media ID: 270.0377)
  - [2/95 GERZ], 1995; 199555 (Box 105, Media ID: 270.0378)
  - [Eldridge street synagogue Yuri and Yana Abayer / Tatiana Shamayera/ Rafael Borukhov], 1995; 199552 (Box 105, Media ID: 270.0379)
  - "What They Remember" MASTER Public Art Fund, 1995; 199553 (Box 105, Media ID: 270.0380)
  - "What They Remember" MASTER, 1995; 199554 (Box 105, Media ID: 270.0381)
  - Tuesday Night Talks / Judith Shea - 3/26/96, 1996; 199557 (Box 105, Media ID: 270.0382)
  - 3/26/96 JUDITH SHEA -Tuesday Night Talks, 1996; 199556 (Box 105, Media ID: 270.0383)
  - Rachel Whiteread - May 8, 1996, 199559 (Box 105, Media ID: 270.0384)
  - Tuesday Night Talks / Rachel Whiteread - May 8, 1996, 199558 (Box 105, Media ID: 270.0385)
  - Magdalena Abakanowicz - Tuesday Night Talks - 9/17/96, 1996; 199562 (Box 105, Media ID: 270.0386)
  - Magdalena Abakanowicz - September, 17, 2996, 1996; 199563 (Box 105, Media ID: 270.0387)
  - Tuesday Night Talks - 10/15/96 - Mary Jane Jacob, 1996; 199564 (Box 105, Media ID: 270.0388)
  - Mary Jane Jacob - October 15, 1996, 199565 (Box 105, Media ID: 270.0389)
  - Wodiczko, Krzysztof - 29 October 1996, 199566 (Box 105, Media ID: 270.0390)
  - Wodiczko, Krzysztof - October 29, 1996, 199567 (Box 105, Media ID: 270.0391)
  - Gregnik Proto II by Gregory Green, 1996; 199568 (Box 105, Media ID: 270.0392)
  - Gregnik Proto I - tape 1, 1996; 199569 (Box 105, Media ID: 270.0393)
  - Gregnik Proto I - tape 2, 1996; 199570 (Box 105, Media ID: 270.0394)
  - Gregnik Proto I - tape 3, 1996; 199571 (Box 105, Media ID: 270.0395)
  - Tuesday Night Talk: Ilya Kabakov / March 11, 1997, 199572 (Box 105, Media ID: 270.0396)